Guide to the Sisterhood is Global Institute Records, 1963-2010 and undated, bulk 1980-2002 RL.01185
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Publications Series, 1981-2003 and undated, bulk 1993-2001, 18 boxes
  - Claiming Our Rights (Box PUB5)
    - Bangla
      - Translation contracts, correspondence with Jaharara Hasan, 1996 (Box PUB5)
    - English
      - 1998, 4 folders (Box PUB5)
    - English (Box PUB6)
      - Invoices, 1996-1997 (Box PUB6)
    - French
      - 1998, 2001, 2 folders (Box PUB6)
      - Amzallag, Yolande, 1999 Sept. (Box PUB6)
      - First draft, Amzallag, Yolande, 1996, 2 folders (Box PUB6)
      - Dabachine, Saadia, 1999 Mar. (Box PUB6)
      - Vivier, Claudine
        - Final edits, 1999 Dec. 3 (Box PUB6)
        - Manuscript, 1999 Dec. 3 (Box PUB6)
    - Hindi, 1999, 1 of 3 folders (Box PUB6)
    - Hindi, 1999, 2-3 of 3 folders (Box PUB7)
    - Malay, 1999, 3 folders (Box PUB7)
    - Persian
      - 1999 (Box PUB7)
      - Dr. Hekmat, Hormoz, 1999, 2 folders (Box PUB7)
      - Drafts, 1996 Nov. 18 (Box PUB7)
  - Claiming Our Rights (Box PUB8)
    - Persian
      - Hekmat, Hormoz, 1998-1999 (Box PUB8)
      - Translation contract, Hekmat, Hormoz, 1996 Oct. 25 (Box PUB8)
    - Russian
      - 1999, 3 folders (Box PUB8)
      - Complete edition with Premises, Filipova, Olga, 1999 Apr. 26 (Box PUB8)
      - Final version for publication, Filipova, Olga, 1999 Apr. 27 (Box PUB8)
      - Russian and Central Asian publication, correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box PUB8)
      - Title page, 1998 Oct. 4 (Box PUB8)
      - Tokhtakhodjaeva, Marfua
        - 1997, 2 folders (Box PUB8)
        - 1998 Oct. 4, 1 of 2 folders (Box PUB8)
  - Claiming Our Rights (Box PUB9)
    - Russian
      - Tokhtakhodjaeva, Marfua
        - 1998 Oct. 4, 2 of 2 folders (Box PUB9)
        - 1998 Nov. 25, 3 folders (Box PUB9)
      - Translation contract, correspondence, Filipova, Olga, 1999 Mar. (Box PUB9)
    - Urdu
      - 1999 Jan. 29 (Box PUB9)
      - Kazi, Seema, 1998 Oct. 4 (Box PUB9)
      - Letter from Vivek Pinto, 1997 Jan. 4 (Box PUB9)
      - Preliminary adaptation
        - Draft, 1999 Jan. 28, correspondence, 1999 (Box PUB9)
        - 1999, 1 of 3 folders (Box PUB9)
  - Claiming Our Rights (Box PUB10)
    - Urdu
      - Preliminary adaptation
        - 1999, 2-3 of 3 folders (Box PUB10)
    - Uzbek
      - 1997, 1999, 4 folders (Box PUB10)
      - Convention on the Elimination of All Forms of Discrimination against Women, in Uzbek, 1998 Sept. 30 (Box PUB10)
      - Correspondence with Polat Abdumannob, 1998-1999 (Box PUB10)
      - Tokhtakhodjaeva, Marfua, 1998-1999, 5 folders (Box PUB10)
  - In Our Own Words (Box PUB11)
    - Arabic
      - 2001 (Box PUB11)
      - Khader, Asma, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box PUB11)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box PUB11)
    - English, 1999 (Box PUB11)
    - Facilitator guide, Nancy Flowers
      - Final draft, 1999 Feb. 11 (Box PUB11)
      - Proofs, 1999 Dec. 17 (Box PUB11)
      - Proofs without crop marks, 1999 Dec. 17 (Box PUB11)
      - Various drafts, 1998, 2 folders (Box PUB11)
    - General guide for workshops, 1998 July 22 (Box PUB11)
    - Proposal, Vaziri, Haleh, undated (Box PUB11)
    - Russian
      - 2000 (Box PUB11)
      - Correspondence
        - Filipova, Olga, 2001 (Box PUB11)
        - Tokhtakhodjaeva, Marfua, 2000-2001 (Box PUB11)
  - In Our Own Words (Box PUB12)
    - Russian
      - First draft and manual for facilitators, 2000 (Box PUB12)
      - Translation contract, Filipova, Olga 2001 Jan. 2 (Box PUB12)
    - Uzbek, first draft and manual for facilitators, 2000 Jan. (Box PUB12)
    - Xanthus design, 1999 May (Box PUB12)
  - Muslim Women and the Politics of Participation
    - Correspondence, release forms (Box PUB12)
    - Hardcover and paperback, 1997 (Box PUB12)
  - Safe and Secure
    - Appendix 1, projects, correspondence, 1998 Aug.-Sept. (Box PUB12)
    - Appendix 3, organization list, undated (Box PUB12)
    - Arabic
      - 2001, 2 folders (Box PUB12)
      - Arabic and English, title page, 1998 June (Box PUB12)
      - Correspondence, correction, 1998-1999 (Box PUB12)
      - Official translation of appendices, UN documents, undated (Box PUB12)
      - Revising and editing by Emira Elias, 1999, 1 of 2 folders (Box PUB12)
  - Safe and Secure (Box PUB13)
    - Arabic
      - Revising and editing by Emira Elias, 1999, 2 of 2 folders (Box PUB13)
      - Translation contracts, revision and editing of Arabic and In Our Own Words, Emira Elias, 2001 Feb. 19 (Box PUB13)
      - Undated translation (Box PUB13)
      - Unofficial translation, Elias, Emira, 2001 Mar. (Box PUB13)
    - Authors
      - Afkhami, Mahnaz, chapter 1, undated (Box PUB13)
      - Nemiroff, Greta, chapters 2 and 4, 1998 (Box PUB13)
      - Vaziri, Haleh
        - Additions for the second edition, 1998 Nov. (Box PUB13)
        - Consultant contract, correspondence, 1998 (Box PUB13)
        - Part 3, 1994 May 14 and undated (Box PUB13)
    - Background material, 1997-1998 (Box PUB13)
    - Bibliography, 1998 Feb. 6 and undated (Box PUB13)
    - Comments
      - On the first edition, 1998 (Box PUB13)
      - Manual evaluation form, undated (Box PUB13)
    - English
      - 1998, 3 folders (Box PUB13)
  - Safe and Secure (Box PUB14)
    - English
      - Draft 1, published Summer 1998, 1998 (Box PUB14)
      - First edition, 1998, 4 folders (Box PUB14)
      - Old version, 1992 (Box PUB14)
      - Published for distribution, 1999 Mar. (Box PUB14)
      - Published for review, 1998 Oct. (Box PUB14)
    - French
      - 2001 (Box PUB14)
  - Safe and Secure (Box PUB15)
    - French
      - Vivier, Claudine, 2001 (Box PUB15)
    - Media, publicity, 1999 Mar. 16 (Box PUB15)
    - Persian, 1999, 2001, 3 folders (Box PUB15)
    - Russian
      - 1999, 2001, 2 folders (Box PUB15)
      - Final editing and revision, Filipova, Olga, 2000 June 4, 2 folders (Box PUB15)
    - Translation contracts
      - French
        - Correspondence with Claudine Vivier, 2000 Sept. (Box PUB15)
        - Vivier, Claudine, 2000 Oct. 30 (Box PUB15)
      - Persian
        - Correspondence with Naghmeh Zarbafian, 1999, 2001 (Box PUB15)
        - Revision and editing of Farsi, Rosham, Mitra, 2001 Apr. 6 (Box PUB15)
      - Russian, correspondence with Olga Filipova, 2000-2001 (Box PUB15)
  - Safe and Secure (Box PUB16)
    - Translation contracts
      - Uzbek
        - 1999 (Box PUB16)
        - First draft, Tokhtakhodjaeva, Marfua, 2000 (Box PUB16)
  - SIGI News
    - 1993 Dec.
      - 1993 Dec. issue (Box PUB16)
      - Alerts, 1993 (Box PUB16)
    - 1993-2000 issues (Box PUB16)
    - 1994 July
      - 1994 July issue (Box PUB16)
      - Materials, announcements, correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box PUB16)
    - 1994 Fall, events and announcements (Box PUB16)
    - 1995 Winter
      - 1995 Winter Issue (Box PUB16)
      - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box PUB16)
    - 1995 Summer
      - 1995 Summer issue (Box PUB16)
      - Materials, announcements, correspondence (Box PUB16)
    - 1995 Fall
      - 1995 Fall issue (Box PUB16)
      - Correspondence (Box PUB16)
    - 1996 Winter/Spring, materials, announcements, correspondence, 1995-1996, 1 of 2 folders (Box PUB16)
  - SIGI News (Box PUB17)
    - 1996 Winter/Spring, materials, announcements, correspondence, 1995-1996, 2 of 2 folders (Box PUB17)
    - 1996 Summer
      - 1996 Summer issue (Box PUB17)
      - Materials, announcements, correspondence (Box PUB17)
    - 1996 Fall/Winter
      - 1996 Fall/Winter issue (Box PUB17)
      - Editing (Box PUB17)
    - 1997 Spring/Summer
      - 1997 Spring/Summer issue (Box PUB17)
      - Correspondence (Box PUB17)
    - 1997Fall/Winter
      - 1997 Fall/Winter issue, books shipped to SIGI-Canada, 1999 Oct. 27 (Box PUB17)
      - Edits (Box PUB17)
    - 1998 Spring/Summer
      - 1998 Spring/Summer issue (Box PUB17)
      - Edited proofs (Box PUB17)
    - 1998 Fall/Winter
      - 1998 Fall/Winter issue (Box PUB17)
      - Costs (Box PUB17)
      - Edited proofs (Box PUB17)
    - 1999 Spring/Summer
      - 1999 Spring/Summer issue (Box PUB17)
      - Costs (Box PUB17)
      - Edited proofs, 1999 Aug., 1 of 2 folders (Box PUB17)
    - SIGI News (Box PUB18)
      - Edited proofs, 1999 Aug., 2 of 2 folders (Box PUB18)
      - Newsletter material, 2 folders (Box PUB18)
  - Sisterhood is Global Book
    - Materials, reference, 1981, 1984, 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box PUB18)
    - Proposal, 1986 Aug. (Box PUB18)
  - Strategizing for Safety
    - 1998 (Box PUB18)
    - Call for papers, correspondence, consultant contract, 1998 (Box PUB18)
- Conferences and Programs Series, 1980-2005, 17 boxes
  Materials on a wide range of events divided into two subseries, SIGI and Other Events. The series contains a large numbers of print materials, posters, ephemeral publications, and newspaper clippings. Individual papers and speeches from some of the conferences are also avaliable. The majority of documents in the series are in English, with some materials in French and other languages. Two oversize posters have been removed to Oversize Materials.
  - SIGI Subseries, 1994-2003 (Box CONF1)
    The SIGI Subseries contains administrative information, conference packages, publicity materials, and correspondence with organizations and individual participants in public events organized or co-hosted by SIGI. Major SIGI conferences include: Religion, Culture, and Women’s Human Rights in the Muslim World (1994), Beijing and Beyond (1996), and Rights of Passage (1997). The SIGI group also contains announcements for Peace Café, a series of panels on women’s roles in armed conflicts and peace-building. The conference Eliminating Violence against Women in Muslim Societies, initially scheduled by SIGI for Sept. 1998, was cancelled and modified into the Expert Group Meeting held in Oct. 1998. The subseries is organized chronologically by year and month, then alphabetically by name of event.
    - 1994
      - Mar., Commission on the Status of Women (CSW)- NGO Consultation, New York
        - General (Box CONF1)
        - Afkhani, Mahnaz materials (Box CONF1)
        - Reports (Box CONF1)
      - Sept., Refugee and Displaced Women in Times of Conflict, Athens
        - Budget (Box CONF1)
        - Correspondence (Box CONF1)
        - Papers (Box CONF1)
        - Participating organizations (Box CONF1)
        - Recommendations (Box CONF1)
      - Sept., Religion, Culture, and Women's Human Rights in the Muslim World, Washington D.C.
        - After conference materials (Box CONF1)
        - Arthur Sackler project (Box CONF1)
        - Book exhibit, 3 folders (Box CONF1)
        - Budget (Box CONF1)
        - Correspondence (Box CONF1)
    - 1994 (Box CONF2)
      - Sept., Religion, Culture, and Women's Human Rights in the Muslim World, Washington D.C.
        - CVs (Box CONF2)
        - Extra papers (Box CONF2)
        - Hotel reservations (Box CONF2)
        - Materials circulated (Box CONF2)
        - Proceedings requests (Box CONF2)
        - Reports (Box CONF2)
        - Speakers file (Box CONF2)
      - Oct., Integration of Women in Commerce and Industry: An Agenda for the 21st Century, Lusaka, Zambia
        - Agenda (Box CONF2)
        - Correspondence (Box CONF2)
        - Proceedings (Box CONF2)
        - Recommendations, organizations (Box CONF2)
    - 1995
      - Mar., CSW Meeting, New York
        - Correspondence (Box CONF2)
        - Documents, papers, speeches (Box CONF2)
    - 1996
      - May, Beijing and Beyond, Washington D.C.
        - Albright meeting (Box CONF2)
        - Book exhibit
          - Applications (Box CONF2)
          - Correspondence (Box CONF2)
    - 1996 (Box CONF3)
      - May, Beijing and Beyond, Washington D.C.
        - Book exhibit
          - Information, orders (Box CONF3)
          - Pending (Box CONF3)
          - Sales (Box CONF3)
          - Writers' comments (Box CONF3)
        - Conference report requests (Box CONF3)
        - Feedback, responses (Box CONF3)
        - General correspondence, 2 folders (Box CONF3)
        - Invitations sent, 2 folders (Box CONF3)
        - Press materials
          - Miscellaneous and book reviews (Box CONF3)
          - Original press package (Box CONF3)
        - Publicity materials, flyers (Box CONF3)
        - Responses to invitations (Box CONF3)
        - Speaker correspondence, invitations, 2 folders (Box CONF3)
    - 1996 (Box CONF4)
      - May, Beijing and Beyond, Washington D.C.
        - Suggested speakers (Box CONF4)
        - Transcripts, 2 folders (Box CONF4)
        - Volunteer help (Box CONF4)
        - Workshops (Box CONF4)
    - 1997
      - Sept., Rights of Passage, Washington D.C.
        - Accommodation (Box CONF4)
        - Articles on women's human rights (Box CONF4)
        - Banner (Box CONF4)
        - Book exhibit (Box CONF4)
        - Center for the Global South (Box CONF4)
        - Claiming Our Rights campaign (Box CONF4)
        - Concept paper (Box CONF4)
        - Conference materials, 2 folders (Box CONF4)
        - Education, literacy contacts (Box CONF4)
        - Friday dinner at Julian's, menu (Box CONF4)
        - General materials, women's human rights (Box CONF4)
        - Hillary Clinton's remarks (Box CONF4)
        - Labels (Box CONF4)
        - List of participants (Box CONF4)
        - Media campaign (Box CONF4)
        - Middle East Institute (Box CONF4)
        - Name signs (Box CONF4)
        - Organization exhibit (Box CONF4)
        - Original materials for photocopying (Box CONF4)
        - Panelists
          - Aidoo, Ama Ata (Box CONF4)
          - Ammar, Nawal (Box CONF4)
          - Arsanios, Afifa Dirani (Box CONF4)
          - Behroozi, Jaleh (Box CONF4)
          - Contact information (Box CONF4)
          - Dharmaraj, Krishanti (Box CONF4)
          - Dutt, Malika (Box CONF4)
          - Flowers, Nancy (Box CONF4)
    - 1997 (Box CONF5)
      - Sept., Rights of Passage, Washington D.C.
        - Panelists
          - Gilbert, Lauren and Herman Schwartz (Box CONF5)
          - Hayes, Diana (Box CONF5)
          - Kazi, Seema (Box CONF5)
          - Khader, Asma (Box CONF5)
          - Maksoud, Clovis (Box CONF5)
          - Mayer, Ann (Box CONF5)
          - Morgan, Robin (Box CONF5)
          - Narayanan, Vasudha (Box CONF5)
          - Nemiroff, Greta Hofmann, 1986-1999 (Box CONF5)
          - Pogrebin, Letty Cottin (Box CONF5)
          - Ross, Loretta (Box CONF5)
          - Shaaban, Bouthiana (Box CONF5)
          - Shefali, Mashuda Khatun (Box CONF5)
          - Tahir, Sharifa (Box CONF5)
          - Thomas, Dorothy (Box CONF5)
          - Tokhtakhodjaeva, Marfua (Box CONF5)
          - Whittington, Sherrill (Box CONF5)
        - Postage (Box CONF5)
        - Poster (Box CONF5)
        - Pre-registration forms (Box CONF5)
        - Press alerts (Box CONF5)
        - Press materials (Box CONF5)
        - Proceedings, distribution list (Box CONF5)
        - Registration confirmations (Box CONF5)
        - Report (Box CONF5)
        - Special invites (Box CONF5)
        - Steering committee (Box CONF5)
        - Travel (Box CONF5)
      - Nov., Middle East Studies Association Conference, San Francisco, Calif. (Box CONF5)
      - Nov., Stanford Symposium
        - Biographical information (Box CONF5)
        - Conference materials (Box CONF5)
        - Global Fund (Box CONF5)
        - Hotel (Box CONF5)
        - Media, poster (Box CONF5)
        - Okin, Susan (Box CONF5)
        - Program (Box CONF5)
    - 1998
      - Sept., Eliminating Violence against Women in Muslim Societies, Amman, Jordan
        - Announcements (Box CONF5)
        - Budget, funding requests (Box CONF5)
        - Book exhibit (Box CONF6)
          - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box CONF6)
          - Invitations (Box CONF6)
        - Conference poster
          - Standard (Box CONF6)
          - Fax version (Box CONF6)
        - Conference proposal (Box CONF6)
        - Correspondence
          - General (Box CONF6)
          - Khader, Asma (Box CONF6)
        - Films (Box CONF6)
        - Funding
          - European (Box CONF6)
          - United Nations Population Fund (UNFPA) (Box CONF6)
          - Request to France Libertés (Box CONF6)
          - Request to Rachel and Ben Vaughan Foundation (Box CONF6)
        - Hotel, meals, other costs (Box CONF6)
        - Invitations
          - General (Box CONF6)
          - Rejects (Box CONF6)
          - Speakers (Box CONF6)
          - Special (Box CONF6)
        - Jordanian National Committee for Women, Sabbah, Amal (Box CONF6)
        - Keynote speakers
          - Bonino, Emma (Box CONF6)
          - Heyzer, Noeleen (Box CONF6)
          - Princess Basma Bint Talal (Box CONF6)
        - Logistics
          - Accommodation, arrival and departure dates (Box CONF6)
          - Interpreters (Box CONF6)
          - Petra, Jordan (Box CONF6)
          - Pre- and post-conference (Box CONF6)
          - Speakers' arrival and departure dates (Box CONF6)
          - Visa, travel advisory for Jordan (Box CONF6)
          - Visas (Box CONF6)
        - Organization presentations
          - Arab Women's Forum (AISHA), Aweda, Sama (Box CONF6)
          - Development of People's Foundation, Canson, Lyda (Box CONF6)
          - Musasa Project, Kwaramba, Rudo (Box CONF6)
          - Sisters in Islam, Anwar, Zainah (Box CONF6)
    - 1998
      - Sept., Eliminating Violence against Women in Muslim Societies, Amman, Jordan
        - Organization presentations
          - Themis, Feix, Virginia (Box CONF7)
          - Women for Women's Human Rights (WWHR), Ilkkaracan, Pinar (Box CONF7)
        - Papers
          - General (Box CONF7)
          - Unsolicited (Box CONF7)
        - Plenary speakers
          - Alsharki, Raufa Hassan (Box CONF7)
          - Bennani, Farida (Box CONF7)
          - Elias, Misrak (Box CONF7)
          - Ghazeleh, Haifa Abu (Box CONF7)
          - Kamal, Zahira (Box CONF7)
          - Kumar, Corrine (Box CONF7)
          - Obaid, Thoraya (Box CONF7)
          - Rouhana, Zoya (Box CONF7)
          - Shaheed, Farida (Box CONF7)
          - Updated schedule (Box CONF7)
        - Preliminary meeting notes (Box CONF7)
        - Postponement, correspondence (Box CONF7)
        - Proceedings requests (Box CONF7)
        - Program (Box CONF7)
        - Registration
          - General (Box CONF7)
          - Cancellations (Box CONF7)
          - Waitlist (Box CONF7)
        - SIGI participants
          - Arsanios, Afifa Dirana (Box CONF7)
          - Flowers, Nancy (Box CONF7)
          - General correspondence (Box CONF7)
          - Kazi, Seema (Box CONF7)
          - Shefali, Mashuda Khatun (Box CONF7)
          - Tokhtakhodjaeva, Marfua (Box CONF7)
      - Oct., Expert Group Meeting on Eliminating Violence against Women and Girls, Washington D.C.
        - Advocacy training schedule (Box CONF7)
        - Budget (Box CONF7)
        - Correspodence
          - Anwar, Zinah (Box CONF7)
          - Arsanios, Afifa Dirani (Box CONF7)
          - Canson, Lyda, Development of People's Foundation (Box CONF7)
          - Feix, Virginia, Themis (Box CONF7)
          - Ilkkaracan, Pinar, poems (Box CONF7)
          - Kazi, Seema (Box CONF7)
          - Khader, Asma (Box CONF7)
          - Kwarmaba, Rudo, Musasa Project (Box CONF7)
          - Obaid, Thoraya, Economic and Social Commission for Western Asia (Box CONF7)
          - Shaaban, Bouthaina (Box CONF7)
          - Shefali, Mashuda Khatun (Box CONF7)
          - Tadros, Marlyn (Box CONF7)
          - Tokhtakhodjaeva, Marfua (Box CONF7)
    - 1998 (Box CONF8)
      - Oct., Expert Group Meeting on Eliminating Violence against Women and Girls, Washington D.C.
        - Correspondence
          - UNICEF (Box CONF8)
        - Expenditures (Box CONF8)
        - Facilitator training (Box CONF8)
        - Invitations (Box CONF8)
        - Logistics
          - Facilities (Box CONF8)
          - Holiday Inn (Box CONF8)
          - Meals (Box CONF8)
        - Materials (Box CONF8)
        - Participants
          - Contact information (Box CONF8)
          - General (Box CONF8)
        - Report, UNIFEM (Box CONF8)
        - Schedule (Box CONF8)
    - 1999
      - Apr., Divorce Iranian Style, Washington D.C. (Box CONF8)
      - Apr., Shaharazad Then and Now, Washington D.C. (Box CONF8)
      - May, Mahnaz Afkhami's visit to Jordan (Box CONF8)
    - 2000
      - Feb., Women's Micro-Credit Projects in Bangladesh and Bolivia, Montreal, Canada (Box CONF8)
    - 2001
      - Peace Café, Montreal, Canada
        - Apr.-May, Correspondence (Box CONF8)
        - May 3, Women as Actors in Peacemaking: The Cases of Afghanistan and Israel (Box CONF8)
        - May 15, Palestinian Women's Role in the Struggle for Peace and Justice, with guest speaker Rima Tarazi (Box CONF8)
        - June, The Middle East: An Experiment in Diasporic Politics (Box CONF8)
        - Sept. Tragedy and the Irrationality of Blame: The Aftermath of September 11, 2001
          - Discussion group (Box CONF8)
          - Meeting minutes (Box CONF8)
      - No month, SIGI events, posters, forms (Box CONF8)
    - 2002
      - Peace Café, Montreal, Canada
        - Apr., Potential guests (Box CONF8)
        - No month, Women's Rights in War, guest speaker Barbara Bedont (Box CONF8)
    - 2003
      - Peace Café, Montreal, Canada
        - Oct., Women's Role in the Palestinian Struggle (Box CONF8)
  - Other Events Subseries, 1980-2005, bulk 1993-2001
    The Other Events Subseries contains announcements and materials related to other conferences, panels, and lectures. The two landmark World Conferences on Women, in Nairobi and Beijing, are extensively represented by numerous documents and declarations produced by the two events. Organized chronologically by year and month, then alphabetically by name of event.
    - 1980
      - July, UN World Conference, Copenhagen, Denmark
        - Mid-decade directions (Box CONF8)
        - Reports (Box CONF8)
    - 1985
      - July, The State of the World's Women, Nairobi, Kenya
        - Brochures (Box CONF8)
        - Clippings (Box CONF8)
    - 1985 (Box CONF9)
      - July, The State of the World's Women, Nairobi, Kenya
        - General, 1-9 of 10 folders (Box CONF9)
    - 1985 (Box CONF10)
      - July, The State of the World's Women, Nairobi, Kenya
        - General, 10 of 10 folders (Box CONF10)
    - 1985-1989
      - No month, Announcements and conference programs (Box CONF10)
    - 1988
      - Oct., SIGN (Sisterhood is Global Network) Dialogues in the Philippines
        - Articles, 2 folders (Box CONF10)
        - Background materials, 3 folders (Box CONF10)
        - Report (Box CONF10)
        - Schedule (Box CONF10)
    - 1990-1996
      - No month, Announcements and conference programs (Box CONF10)
    - 1991
      - May, Who Calls the Shots, the Philippines (Box CONF10)
    - 1993
      - July, UN Human Rights, Vienna, Austria
        - Activities (Box CONF10)
        - Afkhami's interviews (Box CONF10)
        - Correspondence (Box CONF10)
        - Documents (Box CONF10)
    - 1993 (Box CONF11)
      - July, UN Human Rights, Vienna, Austria
        - Post-conference (Box CONF11)
        - Preparatory documents (Box CONF11)
        - Program (Box CONF11)
        - Recommendations (Box CONF11)
        - Reports (Box CONF11)
        - SIGI panel (Box CONF11)
      - Nov., Asian and Pacific Symposium for NGOs on Women and Development, Manila, the Philippines (Box CONF11)
      - No month, Women's Summit, Auckland, New Zealand (Box CONF11)
    - 1994
      - June, Seminar on the UN Convention on the Elimination of All Forms of Discrimination against Women, Lahore, India (Box CONF11)
      - Oct., NGO Forum, Viena, Austria (Box CONF11)
      - Nov., World Summit for Social Development, New York (Box CONF11)
    - 1994-1997
      - No month, Announcements and conference programs (Box CONF11)
    - 1995
      - Mar., Summit for Social Development, Copenhagen, Denmark